Maksym Pidluzhnyi

pidluzhnyi.maksym@gmail.com — portfolio — linkedin — github

Summary — I am a motivated and adaptable developer with a foundation in web development and diverse experience across various technologies and exhibition projects.

My strength lies in quickly learning new concepts, adapting to challenges, and implementing efficient solutions to achieve project goals.

Skills

Frontend HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript **Diverse** GIT, PostgreSQL, Figma, Unity

Backend Java, Node.JS, REST API

Experience

HTW Berlin Okt 2023 – Present

Student Researcher

- Working on imersive technologies within the IDiA project with leading university professors.
- Assist with technical counseling for students.
- Technologies: Unity, Netcode for Unity, XR Interaction Toolkit.

App Smart May 2021 – Mar 2022

Technical Support Level 2

- Customer service by phone.
- Solving problems associated with faulty software as well as hardware.
- Work in CRM systems and ticket services, as well as content processing in the CSM backend

Education

University of Applied Science Berlin 2023-Present

B.S. International Media and Computing Minors: Visual Computing ; Networks

National Technical University Cherson 2015-2017

B.S. Electrotechnics
Minors: Electronics

Achievments

ARS Electronica Festival Sep 2023

- Participating in the festival in 2023 with an installation "Tactile Musical Interfaces".

Deutscher Multimediapreis 21 Nov 2022

- Finalists of the competition Deutscher Multimediapreis.

Languages

German and English

- Advanced

Russian and Ukrainian

- Native